Counseling Center Records UA081
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Counseling Center Records
1986 -- 2015
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Counseling and Mental Health Services
UA081
0.5 Linear Feet 1 box
Arrangement
This collection is organized in two series: Annual reports; and Brochures and pamphlets.
Scope and Contents
The Counseling Center records contain annual reports, brochures, and pamphlets generated between 1986 and approximately 2000.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts University Counseling Service (1971-present) was established in 1971 by the Dean of Students through the Faculty of Arts and Sciences budget. Services are designed to assist students negotiating the ordinary developmental difficulties and turmoil of late adolescence as well as provide counseling and psychotherapy for students with emotional problems (Counseling Center records, 1986-2000). The Counseling Service is currently housed at 120 Curtis Street and is grouped under Tufts Health Services (Facilities Management, (UA021/001).
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Student Affairs and Services; Health and Safety
- Counseling Center annual reports, 1986 -- 1999; UA081.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains annual reports generated between 1986 and 1999.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Annual reports, 1986 -- 1987; UA081.001.001.00001 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1988 -- 1989; UA081.001.001.00002 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1989 -- 1990; UA081.001.001.00003 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1990 -- 1991; UA081.001.001.00004 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1991 -- 1992; UA081.001.001.00005 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1992 -- 1993; UA081.001.001.00006 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1993 -- 1994; UA081.001.001.00007 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1994 -- 1995; UA081.001.001.00008 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1995 -- 1996; UA081.001.001.00009 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1996 -- 1997; UA081.001.001.00010 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1997 -- 1998; UA081.001.001.00011 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Annual reports, 1998 -- 1999; UA081.001.001.00012 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
- Counseling Center brochures and pamphlets, 2000 -- 2015; UA081.002; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains brochures and pamphlets on topic-specific issues from various schools of the university.
  This series is arranged by counseling center at each school and the Drug Free Campus Program.
  - Counseling Center pamphlets for different schools, 2000; UA081.002.001.00001 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Drug-Free Campus Program, 2000; UA081.002.001.00002 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Counseling and Mental Health Service pamphlets, 2011; UA081.002.001.00003 (Box UA081 Shared 1)
  - Counseling and Mental Health Service pamphlets, 2015; UA081.002.001.00004 (Box UA081 Shared 1)